<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teachings on Minh Tang</title>
    <link>minh-tang.github.io/teaching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teachings on Minh Tang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="minh-tang.github.io/teaching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Data Science</title>
      <link>minh-tang.github.io/teaching/intro_ds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>minh-tang.github.io/teaching/intro_ds/</guid>
      <description>Course description Overview of data structures, data lifecycle, statistical inference. Data management, queries, data cleaning, data wrangling. Classification and prediction methods to include linear regression, logistic regression, k-nearest neighbors, classification and regression trees. Association analysis. Clustering methods. Emphasis on analyzing data, programming in R, and comparing methods.
Instructors and TA  Minh Tang (mtang8 dot ncsu dot edu)  Office Hours: Wednesday 10am&amp;ndash;12pm in SAS Hall 5236.  Miao Yu (myu12 at ncsu dot edu)  Office Hours: Tuesday 12:30pm&amp;ndash;2:30pm in SAS Hall 1106.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistical inference on graphs</title>
      <link>minh-tang.github.io/teaching/stat_graph/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>minh-tang.github.io/teaching/stat_graph/</guid>
      <description>Course description The course provides an introduction to and overview of current research in random graph inference, with a particular focus on spectral methods and their applications to inference for independent-edge random graphs. Topics include concentration inequalities; analysis of matrix perturbations; spectral decompositions of graph adjacency and Laplacian matrices; consistent estimation of latent variables associated to vertices; clustering, community detection, and classification in networks; and multi-sample hypothesis testing for graphs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>